[Finn laughing]
Now that I'm letting you
come down here and play,
guess who else gets to
come down here and play?
Who?
[The Man Upstairs]
Your sister.
[echoing]
What?
[Emmet] Well, things sure have
a way of working out smoothly.
Am I right, guys?
[in slow motion] What?
[warbling]
We are from the planet Duplo,
and we are here
to destroy you.
Oh, man!
You're going to have to
get past us.
- Specifically me.
- Oh, it's on!
- Yar!
- [Vitruvius exclaims]
Wait, guys.
There's no need to fight anymore.
I got this.
Yeah, I don't think
that's a good idea.
[inhales deeply] Here we go.
[Emmet] Hello,
visitors from another planet.
You are just as special
as we are.
See? Friends.
[Duplos] Ooh!
- [Emmet] Yes.
- [Duplos cooing]
What do you know? It worked.
Even though we're different,
I guess if we open our hearts
everything can be...
[all screaming]
[gulping]
[burps]
- [gasps]
- More!
[Duplos] More! More! More!
Oh, no!
Attack!
[high-pitched screaming]
[all clamoring]
[Wyldstyle] Run!
[Duplo grunts]
We wanna play
with you, kitties.
♪ Everything is awesome ♪
[MetalBeard]
Fire the laser cannons!
I eat lasers!
That's impossible!
[Duplo]
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la,
La, la, la, la ♪
- [grunts]
- You missed me!
No, I did not!
They're so
adorably destructive!
- [people screaming]
- Hey, guys. Listen up.
Everyone, get along!
Done! Fixed it!
I'm going golfing.
President Business,
you have to stay and help us!
I'm sure you guys can sort
it out amongst yourselves.
You're great at that stuff.
Bye. Gotta go.
- [Duplo giggling]
- [Emmet] Don't worry, Lucy!
Everything can still
be awesome!
[high-pitched screaming]
[Wyldstyle] It wasn't awesome.
We fought them off,
but they kept returning.
[Duplo] Let's dance!
[Wyldstyle]
Every time we rebuilt,
they kept coming after
whatever bright and shiny thing
- caught their eye,
- [upbeat music playing]
and always accompanied
by catchy pop music.
A league of brave heroes
volunteered to chase them
to wherever they came from.
My man! [whoops]
Where's Batman?
He's off having a separate
standalone adventure.
You almost forgot me, guys.
Oh, did we?
I'm literally a lantern.
How did you miss me?
That's my whoops.
Fear not, citizens,
I shall shed...
Guys, can you just reopen the...
Guys, just reopen the...
- [engine powering up]
- You're not gonna?
I don't care, it's just feelings.
Stuff 'em down.
[Wyldstyle] We may never know
if they even made it
to the aliens or were lost
in the dreaded Stairgate.
[wind whistling]
[Wyldstyle] A lifetime has
passed since then. We grew up.
Abandoned anything cute,
shiny, poppy, or young.
And from the wreckage,
we built a grittier,
cooler, more mature society.
We call it Apocalypseburg.
And it is
a heckish place to live.
[Larry] We don't serve decaf!
[Wyldstyle] Show weakness
and you'll be eaten alive.
This new life has toughened
and hardened us all.
Two coffees, please!
One black, one with just
a touch of cream
and 25 sugars.
- [Larry grunts]
- [Wyldstyle] Well, toughened most of us.
Good morning, Apocalypseburg!
Oh! Almost ran me over.
[chuckling] Classic!
- [music playing]
- Good morning! Hello, cyborgs.
♪ I wake up in the morning ♪
- I say Sean Connery!
- Daniel Craig!
I say Roger Moore!
You're crazy! Pierce Brosnan!
- George Lazenby.
- Who?
♪ Everything is awesome ♪
Daniel Craig for life!
Hey! Surfer Dave!
It's Chainsaw Dave now!
Morning, Scribble Cop!
- [growls]
- [laughs]
♪ We're living out a dream ♪
- Morning, Sewer Babies!
- [babies crying]
♪ Awesome ♪
♪ Everything is awesome ♪
This song never gets old.
- [screams] Me organs!
- Oh, sorry!
Oh, good morning, Sherry.
- Scarfield. Deathface, MetalScratch.
- [cats meowing]
Razor, Laserbeam,
Fingernail, ToxinToes...
Jeff.
Hey, Batman!
How was your last adventure?
Good, really good.
Saved the world. Again.
Learned the value
of friendship.
I loved. I lost,
and I'm good with it...
And it's totally on brand for me
to be a loner with a broken heart.
It's what the fans want.
So, yeah,
no, I'm good with it.
Just me and Alfred. [laughs]
- [stifled laugh]
- Not a terse laugh.
And, um, what about you?
[chuckles] Awesome!
♪ Everything is awesome ♪
[Wyldstyle]
Once I was a rebel,
fighting for
a righteous cause.
Now, I only fight to survive.
Everything was awesome.
Now everything is bleak.
- Hey, Lucy!
- Oh! Hi.
I brought you coffee!
Coffee!
The bitter liquid
that provides
the only semblance of pleasure
left in these dark times.
Oh, my goshness!
Did I interrupt you brooding just now?
Ah, this brooding sesh
is not really going anywhere.
Man, I wish I could
brood like you.
Look, all you gotta do is just
stare off into the distance
and then narrate whatever grim
thoughts come into your mind.
What if one day
there was no coffee?
More like,
"War hardens the heart."
"War hardens our hearts..."
Okay, I'm thinking,
it's more like, "War..."
- "War!"
- Hang on.
- "War." No. "War."
- "War!"
- "War."
"War." I can't do this!
I'm too happy to see you.
What's the scariest thing
you can think of?
Oh, come to think of it,
I actually had a nightmare last night.
Nightmares are super broody.
What was it about?
All right, um, so it started
with this dolphin in a top hat.
Uh-huh.
And the dolphin says
in a weird voice...
- [dolphins clicking]
- It's 5:15 p.m.
Oh, I forgot to mention
his chest was a clock.
Okay, I'm thinkin' darker,
broodier, less fish.
Oh, and Batman was there,
and he was covered in glitter.
There was a talking
ice cream cone.
This isn't really
the broodiest.
And then, these scary black
holes open up in the ground.
They started to suck everybody I've
ever cared about out of my life!
And Gandalf was there.
And he shouted...
[Gandalf] It's Armamageddon!
[Wyldstyle] Emmet!
No!
And you disappeared
into the void,
never to be seen again.
Not bad brooding!
[chuckles] Oh! Thanks!
That was definitely
just a dream, right?
Not some vision of the future?
No, no, no.
This is my vision of the future.
A little lower, to the left.
Ta-da!
A house?
Come on! Let me
give you the tour.
Very first one
on the cul-de-sac.
This is the living room,
where you can live it up.
TV room, dining room,
Planty's room,
[whispers] kitty cat room...
Of course, the kitchen,
complete with breakfast nook,
lunchtime nook, and fireman pole.
Which leads to water slide...
Trampoline room...
Monkey-barring
all the way up to...
Toaster room!
So you can have toast
or waffles at any time!
[Wyldstyle] Oh!
And out back,
a double-decker porch swing,
so we can always
hang together!
What do you think?
Uh... Wow. Um...
It's sweet.
It is. It's just, uh...
It's going to attract aliens
and get destroyed.
But maybe it won't.
I just thought
we could rebuild the future.
Make everything awesome again.
[sighs] Emmet...
You gotta stop pretending
everything is awesome.
It isn't.
Every morning,
you walk through town,
singing that terrible,
annoying, manufactured pop song!
[chuckles] That song
really seems to upset you.
- No, it doesn't.
- Oh, my mistake.
That song was fine
when we were younger,
but we also have to
grow up sometime.
Can you do that for me?
Well, yeah. I can try.
But it's easy for you.
You were always a dark, goth rebel.
[scoffs] Yes, of course I was.
- Let's change the subject.
- Okay.
We have to be hardened and battle-ready.
Both of us.
Yeah. No, I get it.
And that's why I've cultivated
a totally hard-edged side
that's super tough
and... Look, look!
A shooting star.
Make a wish! [gasps]
Oh, no!
What? Can't think of anything
to wish for?
I always just wish
for more wishes,
'cause you can never
have enough.
- Emmet.
- What is it?
- [whirring]
- [Emmet grunts] Oh.
[laughs]
[Wyldstyle] Something new.
- Unikitty!
- [yowls]
Recon mission.
Accessing inner
rage!
Let's move out!
[roars]
Hey!
[automated voice] Scan. Scan.
- [upbeat music playing]
- Beep, bop, boop.
Scan. Scan.
Sneak, sneak, sneak.
[upbeat music continues]
[Wyldstyle] We've never seen
anything like this.
They're evolving.
[Wyldstyle] What is it up to?
I don't know,
but that beat is pretty fresh.
[beatboxing]
[beeping]
Uh-oh.
- [grunts] Take it down!
- [inhales sharply]
[all gasp]
- [Wyldstyle] Oh!
- Huh?
Hello! [ringing]
Run!
[screams]
[groans]
[both grunt]
Super-aggro turbo engines!
Super-safe tail light
and blinker.
- Heat-seeking missiles!
- Windshield wipers!
Spiky blaster cannon!
Snazzy racing stripes.
- Let's go!
- [tires screeching]
[grunts]
I told you that house
would attract aliens!
I can fix it.
I'll get us out of here.
[engine revving]
Look out!
[screaming]
[Emmet] Hey! I think my dentist
used to work in this office.
- [Wyldstyle] Focus!
- [both scream]
It's like it knows
our every move!
Weird, right?
- Emmet!
- What?
- Look out!
- No, no, no! [screams]
[Emmet sighs]
- Ultrakatty, flare!
- [growls]
I can't believe
another year has passed.
Wrong flare!
[both singing]
♪ Should old acquaintance... ♪
Alfred, battle cars.
Send out the battle cars.
[grunts] Look on our custom
vehicles and despair!
[warriors chanting]
Custom vehicles!
[both exclaiming]
- We're alive!
[both screaming]
You don't have to keep
whipping me, Deborah.
Welcome to Shark Week!
[dolphin clicking]
[screaming]
- Gotcha!
- Okay, time to panic.
[warriors] Time to panic!
Time to panic!
- [whimpering]
- Time to panic!
- [man] Open the door!
- [woman] Let us in!
Coming. Coming.
Shoes off, please.
I said, shoes off!
Get us home as fast as you can!
Go! Go!
I need angry thoughts,
angry thoughts!
Uh, pollution, poverty,
people who put raisins
in stuff.
It was perfectly fine
without raisins!
[engine revving]
[Ultrakatty screaming]
Love you!
I love you more!
- [ringing]
- Okay, that's adorable.
[all screaming]
Hurry! The door
is slowly closing.
Good thing the door is closing
so slowly and dramatically.
- Whoa.
- Whee!
- Hello!
- Hooray!
- [exclaims]
- [Duplo grunts]
[grunting]
[whimpering]
Eat it and weep.
Eat more and weep more!
Keep eating and weeping.
Weep, eat, weep, weep,
eat, eat, weep, weep!
[grunts] Eat freedom!
You're welcome.
[all cheering]
What in the heck?
[Star Duplo grunting]
[sighs]
Oh, the pain!
[Star Duplo whimpers]
It's getting so cold.
Help me.
I'm General Mayhem.
Intergalactic Naval Commander
of the Systar System.
Open the gate.
No way!
That gate is never,
ever, ever, ever...
Emmet, what're you doing?
Hooray!
See? That wasn't so bad.
Nothing got in.
[screams] Something got in.
[General Mayhem] Bring me
your fiercest leader.
[Batman] Yeah, that's me.
This guy. Coming through.
I'm the leader, obvs.
You? I don't think so.
How many movies
have they made about you?
Because there are nine
about me,
and like three others in
various stages of development.
[grunts] If ye be considered
a leader then why aren't we?
- Yeah. I'm a princess.
- What about me? I'm a space commander.
[MetalBeard] I'm literally
the captain of a pirate ship!
[engine powering up]
- [Benny] My helmet is very blue!
- [Emmet] Wait a minute.
When everyone became
the Special,
didn't we all become leaders?
No offense, I sense no
leadership qualities from you.
My readout confirms you
to be soft,
fragile, and a less than
worthy opponent.
Hey! You watch
what you say about Emmet.
He saved the universe
a few years back.
This guy was a fierce warrior?
Okay, well, technically
I did the warrior stuff, but...
So, you fought and
masterbuilt, and kicked butt,
and then the hapless male
was the leader?
Um, well, you know,
he was a symbol for...
That we all have ideas and...
- But you did all the work.
- Whoa... Hey!
Emmet is the sweetest,
most optimistic guy you could ever meet.
And I know those qualities
are not useful anymore,
and that Emmet isn't changing
with the times,
and lacks a killer instinct,
and in general, just isn't tough enough.
Not tough enough?
Yeah. But this guy is the Special.
Well, at least he was.
Silence.
I don't have room in my ship
to take everyone.
I can fit maybe five.
- Take?
- I'll explain with a memorable jingle.
[upbeat music playing]
♪ Your greatest leaders
Are cordially invited ♪
♪ To a matrimonial ceremony
Tonight at 5:15 ♪
5:15?
Well, if you say 5:00,
people show up at 5:15 anyway.
And if you say 6:00, people start
expecting dinner, it's a whole thing.
- [gasps]
- It's 5:15 p.m.
It's Armamageddon!
[Wyldstyle] Emmet!
No!
Armamageddon is real.
I got this.
You are so handsome.
- And you are very perceptive.
- [ringing]
- [explosion]
- [all shouting]
[all gasp]
[roaring]
[growls]
[meows]
[Wyldstyle grunting]
[grunts] By Jove!
Lucy!
[Wyldstyle grunting]
I RSVP "no"!
- [General Mayhem] You must RSVP "yes"!
- [exclaims]
I'll save you
with my triple-decker couch!
[man coughs]
You know,
maybe let us handle it.
Whoa!
[MetalBeard] You biscuit-eatin'
space lubber! [groans]
Don't need a body.
I'll fight you with me bare... Uh-oh.
Spaceship!
Oh, yeah?
This couch is a convertible.
[all] Oh, Emmet!
You're couchin'
for an ouchin'. [grunts]
- [groans]
- [all] Oh, Emmet!
Thanks for playing.
Oh, no. No, no, no!
No, no, no!
Lucy!
Emmet!
No!
[General Mayhem]
So long, Jerksburgers.
[high-pitched ringing]
[Bianca]
♪ He's gonna come upstairs ♪
[Finn] No! I'm not gonna come
to your dance party right now.
I'm in the middle of
a storyline
- with time travel...
- [Bianca] Please?
[Finn] ...and mind-blowing plot twists.
Stuff you wouldn't understand.
[Bianca] These guys
are coming with me.
[Finn] No, no, wait.
No, no, no.
Stop!
[gasps]
Uh, Lucy? What?
Emmet, what have you done?
Wait.
You guys don't think
this is all my fault?
- Maybe not entirely your fault.
- [cats meowing]
It's totally your fault.
You got that right,
WNBA legend Sheryl Swoopes.
Listen, everyone,
Lucy and the others were kidnapped
in some sort of plan
to start Armamageddon.
Armamageddon?
Where we're banished
for an eternity
into the Bin of Storajj?
- That's just a legend.
- No, it's real!
And it's gonna happen to all
of us unless we rescue them.
Jinkies! Who's gonna
lead the mission?
You wouldn't even make it
past the Stairgate,
let alone survive
the Systar System.
That's a suicide mission.
Wyldstyle said you're
not tough enough to do this.
You haven't changed
with the times.
You're stuck in the past
a quarter score ago.
We've all grown up
except for you.
Yeah, dude,
you're a total Hufflepuff.
- [woman] That's right, he is!
- But I'm not...
You remember what happened
with the Justice League.
Now with Batman gone and
Marvel not returning our calls,
there are no real heroes left.
Only original Aquaman
and unlicensed knock-off,
Larry Poppins.
Well, I say a spoonful of salt
helps the medicine go down.
- Anyone? No?
- [all exclaiming]
- [Gandalf] Oh, Larry!
- [all booing]
[man] Yeah,
what he said is right!
Oh, come on, everyone!
We've done this before.
We all took on Lord Business,
and we changed the world.
We are all special now.
There's nothing we can't do!
We need to go up
to that alien planet,
and show those aliens
what we're made of.
Who's comin' with me?
[sighs]
I'll show them all
how tough I am. [grunting]
[engine powering up]
Hang on
to your fronds, Planty.
We're going to save Lucy...
And all of the other people
who were captured.
[Benny] Spaceship.
Spaceship. Spaceship.
Spaceship.
[grunts] So, this fits five,
you say?
Oh, look at all
these spaceship buttons.
What does this one do?
Oh, what does this one?
What about this one?
- [engine powers down]
- [all screaming]
That would be
the power switch.
[Unikitty] Ooh, what is that?
[General Mayhem]
Behold, the Systar System.
[all] Whoa!
No "whoas." Do not give her the
satisfaction of whoa-ing this.
- [all] Ooh!
- That's even worse!
- [all] Ah!
- Stop it!
[ethereal music playing]
[Wyldstyle]
Wait, that's Batman's job!
[MetalBeard]
Your feet be in me face!
- [all arguing]
- Please be quiet.
I'm trying to make
a majestic landing.
[Star Duplos] ♪ Welcome
to the Systar System ♪
- [General Mayhem] Nailed it.
- [lock chirps]
The queen awaits.
[Star Duplos]
♪ To the Systar System ♪
Uh, am I the only one
creeped out by this?
Uh... No.
[all grunt]
What?
[gasps] Ice cream cone!
Presenting Her Majesty
Queen Watevra Wa'Nabi,
Empress of the Systar System.
[triumphant music playing]
Susan, would you get our guests
something refreshing to drink?
Yes, Your Majesty. [panting]
[continues panting]
Thank you, Susan.
Welcome, guests,
to the Systar System.
Uh, help me out, guys.
What is this? A talking horse?
Sorry about my appearance.
I was in a meeting with the
animal planet of Anthropomorphia,
so I look like a horse.
Thank you.
[laughs]
I'm Queen Watevra Wa'Nabi.
I can change my form
to something else,
if this
makes you uncomfortable.
[in distorted voice]
Hey, guys.
No, go back. The horse
was much more palatable.
Whoever you are, let us go
and stop attacking us!
You started it.
You started it!
What do you want with us?
[normal voice] Trust me,
my plans are totally sinister.
[whispers indistinctly]
- Sincere.
I just wanna help you guys.
All I need is your participation
in a matrimonial ceremony.
No way.
Trust me,
it'll be totally terrifying.
[whispers indistinctly]
Terrific. That's what I meant.
Why are we supposed to
trust you?
I'll tell you
using a universal language.
Is it math?
The language that unites
all the planets in our system.
- [music playing]
- Oh, no. Are we in a musical?
[Batman] Yep, get ready.
♪ Hello, friends My name
is Queen Watevra Wa'Nabi ♪
♪ Don't worry ♪
♪ I'm totally not
One of those evil queens ♪
♪ You've read about In fairy
tales Or seen in the movies ♪
♪ And there's no reason at all
To be suspicious of me ♪
[robots]
♪ Not evil, not evil, no ♪
♪ I'm the least evil person
I know ♪
I won't lie,
it's actually very suspicious
that you're leading with this.
♪ I'm so not a villain
I have zero evil plans ♪
♪ No ulterior motives
Just wanna help where I can ♪
♪ I wanna
shower you with gifts ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm selfless
and sweet ♪
♪ So, there's no reason at all
To be suspicious of ♪
♪ Queen Watevra Wa'Nabi ♪
♪ The least evil queen
In history ♪
♪ And if you do not
Believe me ♪
♪ I totally won't
Imprison your family ♪
♪ 'Cause that'd be evil ♪
♪ And that's so not me ♪
[robots]
♪ I'm not evil, not evil, no ♪
♪ I'm the least
evil person I know ♪
Really? Because I'm getting
super-evil vibes here.
♪ Benny,
do you like spaceships? ♪
♪ 'Cause I think
they are great ♪
♪ How'd you know that?
Loving spaceships ♪
♪ Is my one defining trait ♪
♪ Well, now, my good friend
You can build ♪
♪ The spaceship
Of your dreams ♪
♪ On your very own planet With
your own Spaceship-building team ♪
- [gasps]
- Come on, do not fall for this.
♪ Wyldstyle,
haven't you heard? ♪
♪ There's no reason at all
To be suspicious of her ♪
Yeah, I know
she keeps saying that,
but she's clearly
an evil queen.
Yar, well, I'm not buying it.
♪ MetalBeard, a pirate Without
a ship That's so cruel ♪
♪ It's like a spider
Without a web ♪
♪ Or a queen without a fool ♪
Hey!
Even her metaphors
are suspicious.
♪ I've got a surprise
For you ♪
♪ A planet
That's really a pirate ship ♪
♪ And the population,
your crew ♪
Her story checks out.
She's cool. Not evil.
- What about me?
- Unikitty,
what's the most glitter
you can imagine?
A lot!
- ♪ Times that by infinity ♪
- Whoo-hoo!
[Queen Watevra]
♪ And, Batman ♪
Don't even try it, lady.
I don't need anything.
♪ Oh, I know,
That's why I'm going to give you ♪
♪ Half of everything ♪
Uh, like
"everything" everything?
♪ "Everything" everything ♪
She's rad.
This chick gets me.
♪ Here are some Other adjectives
People use to describe me ♪
♪ Un-duplicitous, un-malicious
Un-conniving, un-nasty ♪
You're clearly just adding "un"
to words that describe you.
Who, me?
♪ I'm Queen Watevra Wa'Nabi ♪
♪ The most least evil person
You'll ever meet ♪
♪ And if you make eye contact
With me ♪
♪ I totally won't have you
Executed immediately ♪
♪ 'Cause that'd be evil ♪
- ♪ Evil ♪
♪ And that's so not me ♪
[applause]
Sorry, we're not swayed by a
little song-and-dance number.
Oh, I liked the tune.
Especially the spaceship part.
And also, no other parts,
just the spaceship part.
Artist to artist, I could tell
it was from the heart.
I knew I would like you.
Game recognize game.
He'll do perfectly
for the ceremony.
I am perfect.
What is this
matrimonial ceremony, buster?
Oh, it's gonna be fun.
I built a Space Temple
right in the center
of our universe.
And at 5:15,
all the stars will align,
and we'll hold a wedding
between me and the Man of Bats.
- [all exclaim]
- The rest of y'all
are gonna be
in the wedding party.
And once we say, "I do"...
[laughs wickedly]
Then you'll get all those
gifts I promised y'all.
You're lying. It's gonna
summon Armamageddon,
and we're gonna get tossed into
the Bin of Storajj forever.
Whoa. No, no, no. No, no, no.
Back up a quick sec.
Did you say "wedding"?
Man, you agreed
to half of everything.
No, no, no. No to the no.
I thought you were the leader.
Uh, yeah, I mean,
I am obviously leader guy.
But I'm not...
Doesn't mean
that I'm ready to settle...
I'm not gonna be the guy
who's gonna make
that kind of a leap...
[tutting] None of us will be part
of your wedding ceremony, ever.
Y'all are so dusty,
tough, and grouchy.
Take them to get changed
for the ceremony.
And this one needs to
get changed most of all.
Whoa!
It's the portal
to dimensions unknown.
The Stairgate.
[door creaking]
I'll just push through
the Stairgate.
Seems simple enough.
[screaming]
Glassteroids!
I can do this.
Torpedoes deploy!
Huh. I can do... [groans]
I can't do this.
[screams]
[grunting]
[gasps]
This is the end!
[rock music playing]
Who was that?
- Where did he go? [screams]
- Hey!
You mind if I save your life?
- Not at all.
- [chuckles] Rad.
[rock music playing]
[screaming]
[pops]
And that's how you break on
through to the other side...
Of the Stairgate.
Who are you?
Whoa!
[chuckles] The name's Rex,
Rex Dangervest.
[announcer] Galaxy-defending
archeologist, cowboy,
raptor trainer, who likes
building furniture, busting heads,
and having chiseled features,
previously hidden
under baby fat.
Whoa! [screams] Enemy ship!
[Rex] That's a negative.
That bad boy is my ship.
Built her myself
out of spare pieces.
Let me show ya around.
Hey, you broke my ship.
Listen, kid,
you can build anything,
but there ain't nothing
you can't break.
[both laughing]
I don't get it.
How about a tour?
Behold, the Rexcelsior.
[Emmet] Whoa-ho-ho!
Are those dinosaurs?
[raptors chittering,
screeching]
[laughs] Whoa!
[Rex] Tell me,
what's a scrapabout like you
doing trying to
go through the Stairgate?
Aliens from the Systar System
kidnapped my friends.
I'm going to get them back.
You don't wanna go anywhere near
the Systar System, trust me.
It's ruled by an alien queen,
and she'll try to brainwash your friends,
so she can use 'em in a matrimonial
ceremony to bring forth...
- Armamageddon?
- Bingo.
You've been to the Systar System?
You can help me.
Forget it, kid.
That place is too terrible.
But I don't like to talk about
my backstory, so don't even ask.
- Oh. Okay.
- There I was,
on a galactic mission.
Ended up being
more than I'd bargained for.
[screaming]
[clattering]
I landed
in the desolate plains
of the dust planet Undar
of the Dryar System.
- [machine rumbling]
- The winds were ferocious.
- [wind whistling]
- The isolation, intense.
[indistinct chatter]
I waited for my friends.
[chatter continues]
Seemed to last forever.
That's when I learned...
There was no one
I could trust but me.
I'm so sorry, Rex.
Don't be. My time alone
was an awakening.
I learned how
the universe really works.
Yeah, I know how you feel.
Ha! You couldn't possibly
know how it feels.
Yeah, I do.
Like you can't ever go back
to the person you used to be.
Even though it was
so much simpler.
- You have to find your own way.
- [raptor chirps]
But you just don't know how.
Hold up a second.
- You have been there.
- Yeah.
What's your last name, Emmet?
Brickowski.
No way.
The visionary
double-decker-couch-building hero
who took it to Lord Business
and had the guts
to face The Man Upstairs?
That Emmet Brickowski?
Yeah.
Dude! Big fan!
Wait, you are a fan of me?
Heck yeah. You're the reason
I started wearing vests.
- Do you like mine?
- Yes, I do!
- [laughing]
- [raptor roars]
Also started wearing chaps,
which are essentially leg-vests.
Wow. You're so much more cool
and grown-up than me.
[gasps] You could teach me!
Rex, help me rescue my
friends, stop Armamageddon,
and teach me to be like you.
Someone Lucy will be proud of.
And I'll be the brother
you never had.
Unless you do have a brother.
I don't really know you that well.
All right, kid, you listen.
You go soft,
you're playing their game.
You're gonna have to grow up
and grow up fast.
Are you ready to do that?
Yes, I am.
I can't hear you.
Really? I was speaking
at normal volume.
Sorry, man. I'm just
a little hard of hearing
from listening to
my mixtapes super loud
with no regard
for my future hearing,
because I live in the now.
Raptors, re-coordinate.
- Really?
- Set a course for the Systar System.
Rex, I promise
you won't regret it.
Kid, I invented the phrase
"no regrets."
I do have one regret
of not trademarking it.
Space cannons.
Hyper-light-speed combustor.
[powering up]
[on speakers]
Super-rad ejector button.
Whoa. Isn't there
a better place to put that?
Raptors, power up.
Crank the warp drive up to 11.
- Times two.
- [raptor chirps]
Yeah!
To the Systar System.
[engine revving]
[Finn imitates engine revving]
[Wyldstyle] That queen
is never gonna break us.
She just wants
to throw a party.
It's clearly a cover
for some catastrophic event.
Yeah. Marriage, am I right?
No one's tying down
this Batman forever.
Ooh, reference!
[scoffs] No. The moment you say,
"I do," it'll unlock some...
- What are you looking at?
- What are you hiding?
What are you hiding?
You're the one with
the reflective mask.
Well, I asked you first.
Well, I asked you second.
- [General Mayhem] Real mature.
- [gasps]
So, where are we going?
[General Mayhem]
Planet Sparkles.
Sparkles.
There, you will get changed
in more ways than one.
Hello!
What was that?
I said,
[in high-pitched voice] "Hello!"
Well, we've been talking
for a while.
I'm not sure
why you're saying hello now...
But fine. Hello to you.
Stick together.
I've got a plan.
Greetings, Bricksburgians.
Welcome to the
Palace of Infinite Reflection.
A self-reeducation
celebrity center.
Namaste.
Ooh! Sounds spiritual.
It is so spiritual.
Sounds like a trap.
This guy's a vampire.
Attractive non-threatening
teen vampire.
I like to talk about feelings,
and how we're in love,
but can't be together.
Isn't that beautiful?
I'll answer that.
It's very beautiful.
The heart wants what it wants.
I also DJ on the side
and wear women's jeans.
Wow!
Guys, we have to stay tough
and gritty.
Do not let them
soften you up...
Oh, yeah. I love getting barnacles
scrubbed off me bilge pump.
Really? Right into it.
[laughing] Oh, oh! It tickles.
- [whirring]
- Whee!
Oh, yeah, I carry my tortured
past in my chiseled glutes.
[scoffs] Even you?
What? I mean,
I'm not gonna turn down a free massage.
She needs extra treatment.
- No!
- Yes.
- First, you'll get a hot gem massage.
- [Wyldstyle exclaiming]
Then an exfoliating
flower beatdown.
- Popsicle face mask and peel.
- [grunting]
- Room-temperature stone contusion.
- [muffled] Hey!
Vegetable observation...
And be cleansed
with a glitter scrub
- and sparkle rinse.
- Ah!
- Next...
- [screams]
- Your hair!
- It's...
- It's beautiful.
- Wait, what?
- [all gasp]
- Oh, no, no, no, no.
- [Unikitty] What? Wow!
- [Wyldstyle chuckles nervously]
Guys, this is not
what you think.
It's so adorable and cute!
Are you covering up
some un-dark past?
No. It's not who I am.
It's just hair.
Look, if I pop it off,
am I Bruce Willis now?
I don't think so.
Well, well, well.
I thought ye were tough.
Looks like the peg's
on the other leg.
- I didn't...
- Is she secretly cutesy?
Look, they did this, okay?
Not me!
[laughing] I mean, what?
I sat in the mirror years ago in shame
and took a permanent marker,
and hair by hair just,
you know, recolored it?
I mean, what kind of crazy
person would do that? Ugh!
Pardon my language,
but she's a real grumpledumpuss.
- [all gasp]
- Take her for some music therapy.
Then she'll be willing
to join our ceremony.
Lucy, where are you?
I'm so sorry.
You're not gonna find her
whispering into a window.
It's time to take action.
Which planet do you
wanna try first?
Um... What do you think?
A tough guy doesn't ask
where to go.
Just pick any of 'em
and act like you're sure.
That's called leadership.
Okay. That one.
Now you're getting it!
- [both whooping]
- [raptors screeching]
Yeah! Now I feel it!
I am feeling it and I like it!
- Everyone, suit up!
- [raptors screech]
[roars]
Only the toughest
are gonna get out
of there alive.
[Emmet] Who's a good boy?
Who's a good boy?
- [raptor squealing]
- [laughs] Yes, you are.
It's 4:30.
The ticking clock is ticking.
Let's go find your friends.
Just a couple of tough guys
being tough. [yelps]
[grunting] Planned that.
[raptors screeching]
[Rex] We'll find
some answers this way.
- [raptor yelps]
- [gasps]
- Where's Cobra?
- [raptors yelping]
Rocky! Quaid!
Ripley!
Connor!
The other one!
[whispers] Nobody move.
I'm tracking unusual activity
on my unusual
activity tracker.
- Not sure what to make of it.
- [alarm beeping]
[chirping]
Huh?
[all vocalizing]
[Rex] Emmet,
don't look 'em in the eyes.
They'll get in your head.
[creatures chittering]
We gotta get out of here!
Go, go, go!
Going, going, going!
[Rex imitating rapid gunfire]
We're surrounded!
[Rex] Don't you let them take advantage
of that big, beautiful heart of yours.
[creature whimpers]
[Rex] Bust through, Emmet.
You can do it!
- [engine revving]
- [yelling]
[creatures shriek]
Hey, I did it!
Nice work!
Yeah, but they're
still coming!
[imitating gunfire]
No biggie. Watch this.
- [yelling]
- Whoa!
- [exclaims]
- [creatures scream]
[tires screeching]
Whoa!
Not bad back there, kid.
You know, you and I are more
alike than you might realize.
Really? I mean, really cool.
Whatever. I don't care.
But how did you do
that punch thing?
You gotta break things down
to build 'em back up.
[grunts] Rex!
Life's impermanent.
Always changing.
You can't hang on to the past.
Otherwise we might as well
all be Kragled.
So deep.
Oh, yeah, thanks.
I've been meditating a lot.
So, it makes sense.
Emmet, listen,
if we're gonna rescue your friends,
you're gonna need to be a...
Master Breaker.
You would teach it to me?
How do you do it?
Well, you have to connect to
some pretty grown-up feelings.
Abandonment. Regret.
Anger at...
A lamppost?
Yeah, lampposts are
the worst because...
Um...
Oh.
[lampposts clicking]
- Hi!
- Hello!
- [all] Good morning!
- [dog barking]
What is this place?
Emmet, welcome to heck.
[overlapping chatter]
[paperboy] Extry! Extry!
[Superman imitating
motor whirring]
- Superman?
- Oh, hey, Emmet.
Superman, what are you doing?
Oh, just mowing my lawn.
Want everything to be perfect
for the wedding ceremony.
Where is it? Where's Lucy?
Where's our friends?
At the Space Temple, you goof.
Wait. Two questions.
One, where's the Space Temple?
Two, why are you here?
What are you talking about?
It's great here.
I never wanna leave.
By the way, "S" stands for "Silly" now.
I'm Sillyman.
Why didn't you come back
for us?
Ah, we're just all having so much
fun here and we're all friends.
- [both laugh]
- I know. What's up, GL?
I see you, boy.
Hey! Oh, here comes Lex
with the smoothies.
Who wants a mango-berry blast
with a reusable straw?
Lex Luthor?
You're friends with your sworn
enemy, Lex Luthor?
Guys, General Zod
just made homemade guac.
- He's a Zod-send.
- [all laughing]
I'm glittery!
- Why are you all acting different?
- [bicycle bell rings]
We all listened to the music,
and it really changed our attitude.
You have to listen
to the music.
Listen to the music
and let your mind go.
- Let's sing him the song.
- That is a great idea, Lexy.
I have an excellent
singing voice.
[in a high-pitched voice]
♪ I'm a soprano ♪
[all laughing]
Oh, we have fun together.
[all vocalizing]
I wanna find my friends.
I don't wanna listen
to a song.
Just listen to the music
and let your mind go.
- Hey! Whoa. Back off. Huh?
- [door opens]
Ow! [grunts]
[General Mayhem] Subject her
to catchy pop music.
That will change her tune.
I'll start with one that's
sure to get stuck in her head.
[pop music playing]
♪ This song's gonna
Get stuck inside your ♪
You gotta be kiddin' me.
♪ This song's gonna get stuck
Inside your head ♪
♪ This song's gonna
Get stuck inside your ♪
[gasping] Not surround sound!
♪ This song's gonna get stuck
Inside your head ♪
- [whimpering]
- ♪ It's so catchy, catchy ♪
♪ It's such a catchy song ♪
♪ It'll make you happy,
happy ♪
♪ Don't try to fight it,
sing along ♪
- [yells] Unikitty!
- Ah!
♪ This song's gonna get stuck
Inside your head ♪
♪ This song's gonna
Get stuck inside you ♪
♪ Run, but you can't hide,
I'll find you Sun so bright ♪
Unikitty, let's get out
of here!
[Unikitty] Wyldstyle!
It's fun! Sing along!
Glitter is like stars
on your body!
My leg is a piano!
This song is stuck in my head,
and my head loves it.
- Join the party!
- No! Guys!
Boom!
[Wyldstyle] What's wrong with you?
You're not acting like yourselves.
This is the most disturbing
thing I've ever seen!
♪ This song's gonna
Get stuck inside your ♪
- Run!
- [people shouting]
Don't listen
to the music, Emmet,
if you want your noodle
to stay al dente!
Emmet?
My body is worming.
I didn't know
I knew how to do this!
Get yourself together.
We'll be safe inside of...
[grunts]
Hey, guys!
[Rex] They're everywhere!
[song continues]
[screaming]
Connor? Ripley? The other one?
Don't be a grumpledumpuss!
Don't you see?
They are trying to change us.
Don't worry, this song has,
like, zero effect on me.
- You're dancing.
- Uh, don't look at me.
Rex! Help me!
[Rex] Think hard thoughts, Emmet.
Think hard thoughts...
Or the rhythm is
gonna get ya! [screams]
[grunts in frustration]
Shoulder, stay still! Stop it!
No! No! No! No! No! No!
Yes!
[song continues, muffled]
[panting]
- Bruce?
- Willis. Yeah.
I spend a lot of time
in air ducts.
I definitely
don't live up here.
I have a home.
- Just scooch on by.
- Ooh.
[song plays loudly]
[song stops]
- [song plays loudly]
- Ugh!
[song stops]
- [song plays loudly]
- [screaming]
♪ This song's gonna
Get stuck inside your ♪
- [singing continues]
- [both panting]
- [Rex gasps]
- It's a dead end!
My CPD,
convenient plot device,
shows there's a planet
right below us.
It's our only way out of here.
I'll hold 'em back.
You bust us out.
I don't know how to do that!
Emmet, I know
you can do this.
What makes you mad?
- A lamppost?
- Come on!
They took Lucy and the others.
And how does that
make you feel? [grunts]
- Not good.
- More honest.
Super not good!
You're getting close now,
brother!
Crack that pain bone open
and suck out the marrow!
What do you feel?
I feel very afraid of losing Lucy
forever and it being my fault,
because I wasn't able
to change!
[yells]
- [all gasp]
- [Green Lantern] Ouch!
[echoing] Whoa!
I did it!
[Rex] Nice job, kid.
How is there outer space
under this sidewalk?
I told you,
nothing in this place makes sense.
- [whoops]
- [inhales deeply]
[laughing] Yeah!
- [Emmet screaming]
- [Rex whooping]
[Emmet] When are we gonna
stop falling?
[Emmet grunts]
- Now.
- [gasps]
- [rumbling]
- Uh, Rex, do you hear a rumbling?
- [Rex screams]
- [Duplo giggling]
Planet Duplo!
[Duplos giggling and babbling]
- This is really bad.
- [gasps]
[woman on PA] Buses are now leaving
for the matrimonial ceremony.
[General Mayhem] Find her.
I must deliver the Man of Bats
to the queen.
I'm not going anywhere.
All right, I stand corrected.
I am going somewhere.
Hmm. More confetti!
More glitter!
More frosting! Mmm!
Oh, I love
the chocolate fondue fountain.
Life is so fragile.
- [device chiming]
- Call from General Mayhem.
Okay. Everybody, take five.
Banana, peel out.
[both laughing]
Hey! You bringin' the Man
of Bats to the Space Temple?
[General Mayhem]
I am on my way.
I just wanna say, I am not okay with...
[groans]
But the one they call
Wyldstyle escaped.
Don't worry.
She'll come to us.
And we'll be ready for her.
[evil laugh]
Sorry. Banana keeps slipping
on his peel on the way out.
[grunts]
[Queen Watevra]
You gonna bruise yo' butt.
- [grunting]
- [laughing]
[Emmet screaming]
[both grunting]
- [Duplo cackling evilly]
- [Emmet whimpers]
[Duplos giggling and babbling]
[Duplo foreman]
All right, you guys.
The queen says we gotta
get these bricks sorted
and up to the Space Temple
before the ceremony starts.
Let's go! Go! Go!
Rex! I think I know
what to do.
What's your plan?
We're gonna have to hang, bro.
I catch you.
Grab and go, amigo! [grunts]
[Emmet] Whoa!
[both grunting]
Well done.
The student has become
the teaching assistant.
Thanks.
I hope this leads
to our friends.
[music playing]
♪ Let's all go to the lobby ♪
[screams]
[Emmet] Yep, I hope
this leads to our friends.
[muffled pop music playing]
I'm having a great time!
Me, too! [laughs]
Yippie!
See, Wyldstyle, it's fun here!
Wait a minute, wait a minute,
wait a minute!
- [music stops]
- Where's Wyldstyle?
- Where is Wyldstyle?
- Where be Batman, too?
What? I can't hear
what you're saying.
- [music continues]
- I'm too busy partying!
[all cheering]
[MetalBeard] Good thing
Wyldstyle's not here!
She would hate this!
[automated voice] Scan. Scan.
Scan. Scan.
Emmet?
[grunting]
[automated voice] Scan. Scan.
[Wyldstyle] Get down!
Emmet!
Lucy! What're you doing here?
- I'm here to save you!
We're saving each other!
Wow. You made it
all the way here.
[stammers] I can't believe it!
You better believe it, sister.
Whoa. Who is this guy?
So, you can see him?
[sighs in relief]
I was so worried
he was just a projection
of what my ego needs deep
down, but, no, he's real. Cool!
I'm Rex Dangervest.
[announcer] Social media influencer!
First baseman!
Man of the soil!
Script doctor!
And my middle name's Machete
Ninjastar, so I know tough.
And Emmet is one tough cookie.
He's a cookie so tough and
hard, you can't even chew it,
'cause it turns out it's not a
cookie, it's a chainsaw.
- Huh, really?
- Yeah. I grew up.
Just like you wanted.
Yeah. No, that's great.
Mmm... I thought
you'd be more excited.
Me, too.
But it's good,
because that's what we need.
They've got all our friends.
Your nightmare,
Armamageddon's coming.
We have to stop it
or we're all doomed.
And it's all going down
- right there at the...
- [Emmet] The Space Temple.
- And the clock from my dream.
- [clock ticking]
It's all coming true.
- [General Mayhem] The Man of Bats.
- Welcome.
- [device chirps]
- [Batman grunts]
Hey, girl, hey.
[General Mayhem] I've detected
a deep emptiness in him.
According to my calculations,
he's lonely.
- Among other things.
- [munching]
I know how he feels.
I mean,
what a weirdo. [scoffs]
I totally
don't relate to that.
The time
for Armamageddon nears.
We must find a weakness.
- If he doesn't say "I do," we...
- Relax, girl.
I got this.
[General Mayhem]
I'll just leave you two alone.
[door closes]
Okay, let's address
the elephant in the room.
Listen, lady, don't try
any mind games.
Batman is a permanent
Bat-chelor.
Can you imagine if having a
family with someone I loved
healed some of
my darkest trauma?
Barf.
There is no way
I'm marrying you.
Well, of course not.
Oh. Uh...
Yeah, but you said that...
I wanted to marry you?
No, no, no, honey.
I was just saying that
to make the person
I actually
wanna marry jealous.
Good. So, I guess
we're done here or...
Marry Batman. [chuckles]
That's a good one. You funny.
[chuckles] Yeah. And, um...
Out of curiosity, why wouldn't
you wanna marry me?
Just, you know, again,
purely for curiosity sake.
Oh, I don't go
for guys like you.
- What do you mean, guys like me?
- [instrumental music playing]
Oh, great. More singing.
Right on time.
Listen, Bruce.
- Who's Bruce?
- It's nothin' personal.
It's just...
♪ I've dated
Men like you before ♪
♪ And you're just
Not my type ♪
♪ My type ♪
♪ Never around during the day
Only come out at night ♪
- ♪ That's late ♪
- ♪ Emotionally wounded ♪
- ♪ Dark and brooding All the time ♪
- Boo-hoo.
♪ Hanging around with clowns ♪
♪ I don't need that
In my life ♪
♪ I ain't Selina Kyle ♪
♪ I ain't no Vicki Vale ♪
♪ I was never into you ♪
♪ Even when you were
Christian Bale ♪
I'm more of
a Keaton guy myself.
Ooh, I loved him
as Beetlejuice.
♪ I'm just not into
Gotham City guys ♪
Oh, yeah, we're flawed,
but that's what makes us so relatable.
♪ I'm just not into guys
Who can't fly ♪
I can fly.
The Batwing can fly.
♪ Rich boys with gadgets
Are not my type ♪
What is your type?
♪ Kryptonian men
Are my kryptonite ♪
Gross!
♪ I'm just not into
Gotham City guys ♪
So what? You dig Superman.
I don't care.
But, like, listen up.
♪ You're clearly
Just confused ♪
♪ Gotham dudes are the best ♪
♪ We have deep, manly voices ♪
♪ And insanely ripped pecs ♪
♪ We're Affleck-level hot ♪
♪ And we're Oprah-level rich ♪
♪ With
George Clooney-level charm ♪
♪ And Val Kilmer lips ♪
♪ We worked for our powers
'Cause we're self-made men ♪
♪ We didn't just get them
From the sun ♪
♪ Like an entitled alien ♪
Go on one date with me
and you'll change your mind.
Unsubscribe.
♪ I'm just not into
Gotham City guys ♪
Give me a chance!
No, thank you. Hard pass.
♪ I'm just not into guys
Who don't wear tights ♪
I used to wear tights.
Ask Adam West!
♪ I'm looking for a husband
Someone to share my crown ♪
♪ And Gotham men are playboys
Who would never settle down ♪
♪ Unlike other superheroes Who
are strong And not afraid ♪
♪ Of commitment
And relationships ♪
♪ I won't name any names ♪
Oh, hey, Batman!
[Queen Watevra]
♪ But I'll give you a hint ♪
♪ He's made of steel ♪
♪ And wears a red cape ♪
[gasps]
Wait!
Please marry me.
Are you sure
this is what you really want?
Yes. Marry me.
And then you'll see,
I am the best at everything,
including commitment.
So, you wanna do this
in, like, 15 minutes?
Make it a quarter of an hour.
[Emmet] Where are we?
Look out!
[all screaming]
[Rex] Emmet,
you got this, bro.
- [grunts]
- Quick! Let's build, uh, a toaster!
- A toaster?
- Just trust me.
[all screaming]
[toaster ticking, dings]
Wow! That was cool.
Oh, yeah, yeah. Yeah?
It was. It was cool.
What fresh nightmare
are they constructing here?
[metal clanging]
[dogs barking]
[Wyldstyle]
It's a wedding cake of doom!
Disgusting!
How is a wedding ceremony
going to summon Armamageddon?
I don't know, but we're not
gonna wait to find out.
We can stop the ceremony
if we find a weakness
in the temple and blow it up.
- [beeping]
- I scanned the layout as we entered
using my Implausitron,
one of my impossibly cool gadgets.
This temple's clearly built as
a beacon for the end of days.
Emmet, you're a construction worker.
What do you think?
Great question, Rex.
I'll take it from here.
Unique construction style.
Seems to be built around this
entertainment center in the middle.
[Wyldstyle] Looks like
a magical relic
that plays music as
a protective defense shield.
Okay, I've got a plan.
We split up.
Rex retrieves the Rexcelsior and
gets in Rextraction position.
Ha! Not a fan of puns? Okay.
Lucy unplugs
this entertainment center,
which should deactivate
the defense shield...
Then I'll do
the Master Breaker punch here,
at the top
of the temple,
which will start
a chain reaction,
causing the whole place
to blow.
Then Rex swoops in,
grabs us and our friends,
and we all go home.
Wow. That's a really
impressive plan.
Thank you. Now grab a headset.
I don't wanna lose you again.
Whoa! Lucy,
what's with your hair?
Oh, it's nothing.
It was just a spa thing.
Don't worry about it.
It's not my real hair.
My real hair's
naturally black.
She's lyin'.
She wouldn't lie to me about something
as important as her hair color.
- I'm not.
- [Rex] She would
if she was brainwashed.
And you can't wash a brain without
washing the hair on top of that brain.
It's basic science.
Lucy, you're not...
[laughing] No.
[gasps] Are you?
[scoffs] I'm not!
I'm not brainwashed!
What about the rest
of our friends?
Oh, they're brainwashed.
But I'm not.
You sure we can trust her?
Emmet?
It's me.
I can always trust you.
Now, you disconnect the shield,
and I'll blow up the temple.
And I'll get my ship.
We've got no time
to lose, because...
- [clock ticking]
- It's 5:00 p.m.
[Batman] "The union
of Queen Watevra Wa'Nabi
and Bruce Margolis Batman."
I will say it is nice
that you have a vegan option,
but we're gonna have to
reprint these all in black.
- Bam!
- I like it.
And instead of releasing
doves, how about bats?
- [bats screeching]
- Ta-da!
Sweet! I got an idea.
What if, instead of throwing a
bouquet, if I throw a batarang,
and whoever's chest
it lodges in
is the next to get married?
[chuckles] Love it, babe.
I did not expect this
to be so much fun.
Who would've thought that
this incorrigible gadabout
would ever tie the knot?
People change. I change,
like, every five seconds.
Like this, boom.
Oh. Uh-huh. [chuckles]
I mean, this morning
I was all alone.
Living in a giant palace with
only a fussy British servant,
and no one
who could really relate to me.
I can really relate to that.
But along the way,
it got real.
So, so real.
Look at us,
two different worlds.
Two people
who just need someone
who understands us...
[both] To find real happiness.
- Whoa! Jinx.
- Jinx!
[both] Jinx.
And final jinx.
Oh, you're so jinxed,
both of you, aren't you?
So, let's stop this forever.
Have you been here
the whole time?
Yeah. And I'm sad about it.
[General Mayhem]
So, then the centaur says,
"That's not the half
I'm talking about."
[all laughing]
Okay, target detected.
I'm closing in.
- [Rex] 10-4, good buddy.
- [Emmet] 10-4 you, good buddy.
[Rex] You're the good buddy,
buddy.
- [Emmet] Is that Bruce Willis?
- [Bruce Willis] Hey, guys.
[Rex laughing]
Good one, Bruce Willis!
Get to the bridal suite
without getting brainwashed.
Think hard thoughts.
Brood. Brood. Brood!
Brood!
Did you just say "brood"?
No, "bride"!
I need to see the bride.
I'm sorry, no entry allowed.
Who are you?
Who, me? [laughing]
I'm your worst nightmare.
You're me when I'm late
to school,
and I forgot my homework and
my pants are made of pudding?
No, I don't... [grunts]
- [punches landing]
- [grunting]
[Queen Watevra] Mayhem!
Is everything in order for the ceremony?
Yes, I will operate
everything here
from this
home entertainment center.
There it is.
[Batman] You so get me.
No. You so get me.
No, no, no. You so get me.
They brainwashed Batman.
Wow, they're good,
because he is dense.
Let's both say the first word
that pops in our heads
and see if it's the same.
- Okay.
- One, two, three.
- Party!
- Batman!
Oh, that's crazy,
'cause Batman is all for partying.
- So, that's basically the same word.
- Totally.
Totally.
Final totally. And end it.
We've gotta get upstairs.
The show's starting.
Mayhem,
do the boopity-bop-bop.
[automated voice]
Boopity-bop-bop.
Bring down the house,
my queen.
This house is about to
get tore up.
We've been expecting you.
Then expect the unexpected!
[General Mayhem]
Did you expect this?
- [grunts] Yes.
- [groans]
[General Mayhem] Well,
I expected your expecting our expecting.
And I expected your expecting
of my expecting your...
Wait, now I'm lost.
[Star Duplos] Yay! Whee!
[both yelling]
[grunts]
[groans] I feel dizzy.
[retching]
[crowd cheering]
Citizens of the 11 planets
of the Systar System!
I ask you
to put your hands together
and apart, and together again
in a repeated fashion.
[rhythmic clapping]
[Emmet] Broody Judy,
this is Stubble Trouble.
What's your status?
- Hello? Lucy?
- [static on radio]
She's not answering.
- Uh-oh.
- Is that bad?
An "uh-oh"? Never good.
I thought she might've been
more brainwashed
than she was letting on.
No. No, not Lucy.
She is the toughest there is.
Unless that song got stuck
in her head.
Lucy. Lucy?
- Come on, Lucy, where are you?
- [grunting]
Allow me to introduce...
The wedding party.
Supporting the bride
are Marie Curie...
Chocolate Bar...
The Tin Man...
And Ruth Bader Ginsburg.
Bearing the rings, Banana.
Okay, okay. You can do this.
Don't mess this... [yelps]
- [crowd groans]
- I messed it up! I messed it up!
[grunting] No!
- [crowd gasps]
- I'm slipping! Don't look at me!
No! [groans]
- [crowd gasps]
- This is my nightmare!
I had a dream about this!
Don't look at me!
[Ice Cream Cone] And on the groom's
side, MetalBeard...
[plays trumpet] Arr!
- [Ice Cream Cone] Unikitty...
- Hi!
[Ice Cream Cone]
And that spaceman, Benny.
Spaceship!
Oh, no, my friends.
I barely recognize them.
Don't worry
about your friends.
Don't worry about Lucy.
Focus on what you need to do.
Visualize your success.
[echoing]
[grunts]
- [rumbling]
- He did it!
He's so tough!
We were so wrong about him.
Way to go, Emmet.
You've changed, perfectly.
Your future is bright.
Right now, we gotta deal
with the present.
Wow! My own Rex Vest?
[laughs]
Thanks for helping me change
for the tougher.
Don't thank me,
thank yourself.
Catch you on the flip. Hey-yo!
[Wonder Woman] Uh-oh.
Ugh! I left my lasso in there!
And now presenting
Queen Watevra Wa'Nabi...
Hey!
[Ice Cream Cone]
And also Batman.
- [rock music playing]
- Commitment!
[powering up]
You look beautiful.
You look stunning.
You are so right.
I know this is
a strange thing to say
to the person
I'm about to marry,
but I actually think
I really like you.
Samesies.
- Totally. Totally.
- Totally.
And bring it to a merciful end.
Can we start now?
- Supes!
- [sighs]
I'm getting hitched.
Feeling jelly?
Not at all!
Oh, it's burning
you up inside.
[General Mayhem] You don't
understand who the queen is
and what we're trying to do.
She's trying to
attack us, obviously.
You attacked us!
No, you started it.
[both grunting]
Well, now I'm gonna end it.
- [Heart Bomb Duplo] Hello!
- [General Mayhem] No!
[General Mayhem screams]
[General Mayhem groaning]
[gasps]
Help me. Please.
Okay, I'm not falling for it.
No. Uh-uh.
No way.
[whimpers]
Nope. Mmm-mmm.
Nope. Stop.
Uh-uh. No. Ugh!
No, I will not care about...
[gasps, screaming]
[panting]
[both grunt]
[both panting]
You do care.
I knew there was some
sweetness under that darkness.
What are you talking about?
You're the bad guys, okay?
Maybe in your world.
But here, we don't see it that way.
Okay, no, no, no. Uh-uh.
Your whole costume and mask
and all the stomping around acting
like you're the boss of us...
Because it's the only way
you'll listen!
I tried to wear a mask
and talk tough,
a language I thought you'd understand,
and it totally did not work.
All we wanna do is
unite our worlds in peace.
Why didn't you guys
just tell us that?
We tried.
The queen sang a whole song
about how not evil she was.
That was the truth?
You guys
are terrible communicators.
[sighs] I know.
Come with me.
For years, we've tried to join
you, to play with you.
But you've always
pushed us away.
Now all of our fighting has brought
us to the brink of Armamageddon.
But this wedding
can change all that.
Bring us together
and stop Armamageddon.
It'll make
everything awesome again.
But everything isn't awesome,
it's, it's, uh...
- [gasps]
- [crowd cheering]
[Ice Cream Cone] And now,
the queen will change
into her original form.
- [crowd cheering]
- [gasps]
See? Friends.
[Duplos] Ooh!
The queen was from Emmet.
Those bricks
inspired our world.
We exist because of you.
You started it.
We started it?
You started everything.
We look up to you.
Always have.
[MetalBeard] Wyldstyle!
[Benny] Where have you been?
- Oh, you guys aren't brainwashed?
- [upbeat music playing]
[laughing] Brainwashed? No!
We're just happy.
It's so much more fun here.
There are so many more
spaceships on this adventure!
And yet not nearly enough.
Wait, if you guys are good,
then who's the bad guy?
Stubble Trouble,
this is Alpha Wolf-Bro Dog.
I'm almost
in Rextraction position.
What's the color
on the ground?
[Emmet whispers] Fuchsia.
Rex, I see Lucy.
But she isn't taking down
the shields.
[Rex] You don't need Lucy.
You don't need anyone.
If you focus,
you can make a punch so powerful,
you'll take it down,
shields and all.
You've got the power
inside you.
I can do this. I can do this.
I can't not do this.
So glad you aren't gonna
destroy this ceremony.
If anything bad were to
happen, we'd all be doomed.
But luckily, there's nothing
to worry about now.
Oh, no.
Emmet.
[gasps]
[grunting]
- Emmet!
- Lucy, what are you doing?
Did you draw stubble dots
on your face?
What? No. [chuckles]
Listen to me.
I was wrong about the queen.
No. No, no, no.
- Rex was right about you.
- No, you can't do this.
You're just stopping me
because you're brainwashed.
I'm not brainwashed!
That's exactly what a
brainwashed person would say.
[MetalBeard] Ahoy, Emmet.
What happened to you?
A betoughening, it seems.
[Ice Cream Cone]
Do you, Queen Watevra,
take Batman to be your
special best partner?
I do.
Hurry up, kid,
we're running outta time.
Guys, get out of my way.
If you want to do harm
to yon wedding,
you will have to
get by we first.
I'm sorry,
but this is for your own good.
[yells]
[all screaming]
Emmet! Come back!
[grunting]
Don't do this.
[Rex] Don't listen to her!
Almost there...
Oh, come on! No!
Not all the way down!
[Wyldstyle] Stop, Ems.
You don't know
what you're doing!
This isn't the real you.
This is the real me.
- The truth is, this is my real hair.
- [gasps]
I used to sing and dance
and have colorful hair.
And I even loved
"Everything Is Awesome."
No, no. You would've told me.
You hate that music.
It isn't you.
Yes, I darkened my hair
with marker,
'cause I wanted people to
think I was cool and grown up.
And then I tried to change you
into someone tough, too.
And I was wrong.
I like you the way you were.
Sweet, innocent, kind.
The real Lucy
would never say that.
[Ice Cream Cone]
Do you, Batman,
take Queen Watevra
- to be your special best partner?
- [Emmet yelling]
[Batman] I do, uh...
- Emmet!
- [yelling]
[both grunting]
[Wyldstyle grunts]
[all bawling]
What's happening?
What did I just do?
- [rumbling]
- [gasps]
Lucy!
- Come with me.
- I got you, brother.
- [Wyldstyle] Wait!
- [chirps]
Emmet.
Lucy!
[gasps]
[screaming]
[Wyldstyle] What's happening?
Where am I? What...
You shouldn't take my stuff!
[Bianca] You crushed
my space laser cake thingy!
[Wyldstyle] Emmet?
Rex, why are we leaving?
We gotta save my friends.
Do we? They didn't come to
save us when we were all alone.
What are you talking about?
Who are you?
Look a little closer.
We're not so different.
What, you and I?
- We and us.
- Huh?
Emmet, I'm you.
But I'm me.
I'm you from the future,
all grown up.
Wait, if you're me,
why do we sound so different?
[in Emmet's voice]
Why do we sound so different?
[gasps]
It's a mind-blower, I know.
That's why I was so cagey
in telling you my backstory.
Actually, you kept
bringing it up.
There I was, you.
In that little house-ship,
trying to make it through the Stairgate.
[screams]
This is the end!
[screaming]
[Rex] There was no handsome,
older version of myself to save me.
[Finn] Where's Emmet?
[The Man Upstairs] Honey,
I'm on my way out the door,
but the kids are fighting.
Bye!
[Mom] Guys! Please,
find a way to play together,
or I'm gonna have to ask you
to put it all into storage.
- [Bianca] But, Mom...
- [Mom] No buts.
This is the last time.
[Emmet] Help! Anyone?
Hello?
[Rex] No one heard me.
No one came for me.
I was left behind. Forgotten.
While the rest of my so-called
friends danced and sang
at the hands of a monster.
What could I have done
to avoid such a fate?
[Wyldstyle] We also have
to grow up sometime.
[Abraham Lincoln] Wyldstyle said
you're not tough enough to do this.
[General Mayhem]
This guy was a fierce warrior?
[Surfer Dave] Yeah, dude,
you're a total Hufflepuff.
[echoing]
[Rex] I was alone with nothing
but anger.
But anger was the key
to my freedom.
[yelling]
[grunting]
It was time for me
to take a stand.
[grunting]
I was real.
I was no longer the
naive Emmet I used to be.
I got myself a new vest,
a new head of hair,
and a petulant attitude
towards everything that's lame.
I gave myself a makeover
and became Rex.
[announcer]
Radical Emmet Xtreme.
[Rex] I was all grown up,
but I still wasn't free.
I knew the only way
to move past it
was to make sure it never
happened in the first place.
[Bianca] It's a dance party!
[Rex] And then I saw a way
to undo all the unbearable
pain I'd experienced
in one convoluted move...
Called time travel.
Sorry, Doc,
gonna need your DeLorean.
And, Bill, Ted,
your phone booth.
Doctor Who's TARDIS.
H.G. Wells' bicycle thing.
Whatever Skynet's been using.
And this hot tub.
I built a time-traveling
spaceship
- and blasted into the past.
- [electricity crackling]
- I picked up a crew.
- [raptors screeching]
[Rex] Then I traveled
to the moment right before
I was thrown into the cold,
dark truth of the world.
And I found the one person
I wanted to protect.
- Whoa!
- [Rex] Me.
I was following everything you
said, except for...
Everything after the part
where you said, "I'm you."
Literally the first thing
I said.
This time travel stuff's
always kinda confusing.
It's best just to go with it.
You tricked me
into hurting my friends?
I didn't trick you.
I taught you to harden your heart,
just like you asked me to.
What did you make me do?
What exactly is Armamageddon?
- [indistinct arguing]
- [Finn] You stole my guys.
This is your fault.
What's going on up here?
[Finn] She took my guys
and she ruined them.
- [both arguing]
- All right, all right!
[Wyldstyle] Armamageddon.
Our-mama-gets-in?
Okay. Really?
[exclaiming] Guys.
I know I said it was the last
time, the last time,
and the time before that.
But this is the last...
Last time.
I need... [screams]
I stepped on a brick.
[breathes deeply] I'm just...
I'm doing breathing,
so that it takes the pain away.
I need... [screaming]
[groaning]
Close to childbirth.
Very close in pain level to childbirth.
[inhales deeply]
You guys
know the consequences.
I need you guys to put
all the bricks into storage.
[Wyldstyle]
The Bin of Storajj.
- No, no, no, Mom, please.
- Please, please. One more chance.
Finn, I want you
to go downstairs
and put away your
dystopian wasteland thing.
- It's Apocalypseburg.
- I don't care what it's called.
Bianca, I need you
to clean up here.
Mom, it's not fair.
[Mom] Look, I'm not
the bad guy in this story.
I'm just an amusing
side character.
- And you're the one who took my guys.
- How is it my fault?
[Mom] Hon, I could really
use your help up here.
[The Man Upstairs] Kids, do the thing...
Uh, what your mother said.
You heard your father's
super helpful contribution.
[sighs]
You ruined everything.
I just wanted you
to play with me.
[Wyldstyle]
Emmet, what have you done?
What have we done?
[Rex] It's called growing up.
Isn't that what you wanted?
No. I wanna save my friends.
You don't have friends.
They're just pieces of plastic.
[chuckles] You still want to
go back
- to the Matrix when you know the truth?
- What's the Matrix?
It's a movie only cool, older,
mature dudes like us have seen.
It's time to put away
childish things.
No.
My friends may not be real to
you, but they're real to me.
And they're my family.
I won't give up on 'em.
I am so disappointed
in myself.
I guess you're gonna have
to become me the hard way.
Ain't something
a couple of years
in Undar of the Dryar System
won't fix.
No. No, Rex.
Or me, or you...
[stammers] Please, no! No!
One love.
[Emmet] Wait, wait, wait.
What are you doing?
[screaming]
It can't be this hopeless,
can it?
It can.
[Gandalf] It's Armamageddon!
[woman] Look out,
Chainsaw Dave!
It's Purgatory Dave now! Whoa.
[all screaming]
I had theater tickets
tonight! No!
No! I was finally valued!
Cannonball!
[screaming]
Not gonna slip this time!
[cheers] I did it! No!
No! My queen!
- [screaming]
- No, no, no!
No! My queen!
No! Don't leave me!
My queen!
[screams]
[Wyldstyle] No, no! But...
Stop it! I said stop!
Can you please,
please help us?
[clatters]
[door closes]
[Emmet] War hardens the heart.
[Wyldstyle] Wait. What? No!
This isn't the end!
It can't be.
This isn't one of those things
with a downer cliffhanger ending.
Uh-uh. No, no.
This needs to have a happy ending.
Seems like a downer to me.
And so it ends for Batman,
the way it began.
In darkness.
[Green Lantern muffled]
Hey, uh, Supes.
You're, uh, pressed against me.
It's no rush or anything.
No! No, no, no!
It's only over if we give up.
Well, it's over
and we're giving up.
We can get out of here
if we all rally together.
No. It's too late.
Nothing left to do except sing a
mature, sad song as we fade to black.
♪ Everything's not awesome ♪
- Wait, what?
- Wyldstyle was right.
♪ Everything's not cool ♪
♪ I am so depressed ♪
♪ Everything's not awesome ♪
Preach, brother.
♪ I think
I finally get Radiohead ♪
Bro, you should check out
Elliott Smith.
♪ What's the point?
There's no hope ♪
♪ Awesomeness was
A pipe dream ♪
Guys! Come on!
♪ My spirits be at the bottom
Of the sea ♪
♪ Love's not real
I just wanna eat carbs ♪
♪ Pass the ice cream ♪
I'm not a thing you can just use
to fill emotional voids with.
Stop! Everyone, okay,
just listen.
♪ Everything's not awesome ♪
Uh, yeah, we know.
That's why we're singing about it.
♪ But that doesn't mean
That it's hopeless and bleak ♪
How so?
♪ Everything's not awesome ♪
♪ But in my heart I believe ♪
♪ I believe ♪
[both]
♪ We can make things better ♪
♪ If we stick together ♪
[all]
♪ Side by side, you and I
Can build it together ♪
♪ Yeah, build it together ♪
♪ Build it together ♪
♪ Together forever ♪
♪ All together now ♪
♪ This song's gonna get
Stuck inside your ♪
[song continues in distance]
Lucy! [grunts] I'm over here!
♪ This song's gonna get
Stuck inside your ♪
♪ Heart ♪
[straining]
I'm over here!
[grunting]
- Lucy?
- [footsteps approaching]
Nope.
I tried to break your spirits,
but now I'm gonna
have to break you.
- No! No!
- Chi-cha!
[Rex] This is gonna be easy.
You're weak.
[Emmet] No.
You're the one who's weak.
Huh?
[grunting]
I'll never grow up
to be like you.
It's easy to
harden your heart. [grunts]
But to open it...
That's the toughest thing
you can do.
I'm gonna grow up.
But I won't stop caring
about the people in my life.
They may see the world
differently, but that's not bad.
I think it's inspiring.
[Finn] It can be
whatever you want it to be.
[Emmet]
Because everything's...
Not awesome.
But we can make it a little
more awesome if we remember...
We're not alone in this world.
We're in it together.
[blocks clicking]
What's going on?
I'm back, everybody!
My queen!
[straining]
[Batman] My queen!
Watevs, I thought I lost you!
Babe, I thought I lost you!
All right, everyone.
You wanna get our worlds back?
Then we've gotta save Emmet
and stop Rex Dangervest.
♪ Everything's not awesome ♪
♪ Things can't be awesome
All of the time ♪
♪ It's an unrealistic
Expectation ♪
♪ But that doesn't mean
We shouldn't try ♪
♪ To make everything awesome ♪
♪ In a less idealistic
Kind of way ♪
♪ We should maybe aim
For not bad ♪
♪ 'Cause not bad right now
Would be real great ♪
♪ I'm driving the spaceship
I'm back in command ♪
♪ I'm turning the switch,
and I'm... ♪
- Calm down.
- Don't touch me when I'm spaceshipping!
[all laughing]
I like your
"Stop Rex" plan, Lucy.
One small question, who's Rex?
This is gonna sound crazy,
but I think
he's a version of Emmet
from the future
that I wanted him to be,
but he turned out
to be a real jerk.
That's a really
cute speech, Emmet,
but actions speak louder
than words.
Yes, they do.
[Rex grunting]
My friends are coming to rescue
me and you can't stop them.
- [Rex grunts]
- [yells]
Raptors, to the Rex-Wing
fighters.
Don't let them near the Dryar System.
Copy? Over.
- Uh-oh.
- [raptors grunting]
Now, Unikitty!
Glitter hairball missiles, go!
[retching]
[Benny] Spaceships!
Spaceship!
Fire the sprinkle cannon!
You lollygagging lizards!
No! I'm not gonna
lose you again!
I'm saving you.
[Batman] I'm saving you.
I'm sacrificing myself
for you!
[Batman]
I'm sacrificing myself.
- I am.
- I am!
[Ice Cream Cone] You know what?
I actually like this now.
[Rex] This isn't
even happening.
It's all just the expression
of the death of imagination in
the subconscious of an adolescent!
Ow! I don't even understand
what you're saying!
Don't worry.
You don't have to.
[Rex laughing evilly]
[Wyldstyle] We're surrounded!
[Sweet Mayhem]
We can't go any further!
I'm not giving up!
[Sweet Mayhem]
You won't make it! No!
[yelling]
[Rex grunts]
[wailing]
Guess your so-called friends
didn't save you after all.
[Rex laughing]
[Wyldstyle] Oh, yeah?
- [Rex] Huh?
- Who you calling "so-called"?
Lucy! You saved me!
You came back for him.
Well, you're too late.
I'm just gonna keep going back in
time until I get this thing right.
- Heart attack!
- [Duplo grunting]
[Duplo laughs]
[both grunt]
[gasps]
Goodbye!
[explosion]
[sizzles]
It's over, Rex.
Emmet's never going to be you.
But you can be like him.
You don't have to be
the bad guy.
You can join us.
[grunts]
I can't.
What do you mean?
She came back for you.
You're never going to turn out like
me, which means...
I'm never going to exist.
Wait. Wait, no.
[laughs] Look! I knew it!
Look, I'm Back To The Futuring!
Totally called it.
What's Back To The Futuring?
It's a classic movie
older kids get to watch.
And now it's happening to me.
Come on! Take our hand,
while you still have a hand to take!
That ain't how it works, kid.
Rex...
[Rex] It's okay.
I'm proud of ya.
And you're gonna grow up
to be better than me.
But kind of thanks to me,
so I'm also great.
And, Lucy,
thanks for coming back for us.
Besides, this is a pretty
righteous way to go out!
No regrets!
Except, again,
not trademarking "no regrets."
That was a mistake. One love.
Just to be clear, that really happened.
You could see him, right?
- Uh-huh. Time to go?
- Yeah.
[Wyldstyle] Hey, um...
I'm really sorry
I tried to change you.
[Emmet] Oh, I'm sorry I blew up the
wedding and almost banished everyone
to an eternity of lifelessness
in a cosmic storage bin.
It's fine.
[Wyldstyle] Can we be
special best friends still?
[Emmet] Fo' eva.
[kids chattering loudly]
[Bianca] Hey! Hey!
Pony's at the dance party.
"What kind of dance party is this?"
[Bianca] In there! Do not!
Oh! We're going down!
It's eating the queen!
[The Man Upstairs]
Honey, where are my pants?
[Finn] Take off!
[both] Good morning,
Syspocalypstar.
Good morning, sparkle babies!
Hello!
Let's switch helmets.
[Benny in deep voice] This
makes my voice sound awesome.
Scarfield, Deathface,
MetalScratch...
Ripley, Connor, the other one.
Wait a minute. Where's Jeff?
- [raptor retches]
- Meow.
[device whirring]
Guys, hold on! Hold on!
Hold on! Terrible news!
I missed a gimme putt
for birdie on seven.
Anyway, you fix everything that
was going on? All the crazy stuff?
- [Benny] Spaceship!
- [screaming]
Hot! Hot! Hot! Uh-oh.
[screaming]
- [Unikitty] Yay!
- [Benny laughs] Yeah!
I've got a surprise for you.
Our house!
Planty!
An original album
of "Everything Is Awesome"?
Wait a minute. Is that...
[gasps loudly]
♪ Unbelievable, super cool
Outrageous and amazing ♪
♪ Phenomenal, fantastic
So incredible ♪
♪ Unbelievable, super cool
Outrageous and amazing ♪
♪ Phenomenal, fantastic
So incredible ♪
♪ It's the credits! ♪
♪ Yeah, that's the best part ♪
♪ When the movie ends ♪
♪ And the reading starts! ♪
♪ You can keep
Your adventure ♪
♪ And all that action ♪
♪ 'Cause the credits Of the
film Are the main attraction ♪
♪ And don't even
Think about tryin' to leave ♪
♪ Or you might miss a name ♪
♪ Like Pam or Steve! ♪
♪ Both incredible names
So let's stay in our seats ♪
♪ And read a credible list
Of their incredible feats! ♪
♪ 'Cause we're all
Like a team ♪
[woman] Let's go.
♪ Livin' inside a dream ♪
♪ You and me doin' our thing
And we'll fly ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Unbelievable, super cool
Outrageous and amazing ♪
♪ Phenomenal, fantastic
So incredible ♪
♪ Woo-hoo! ♪
♪ Unbelievable, super cool
Outrageous and amazing ♪
♪ Phenomenal, fantastic
So incredible ♪
♪ Woo-hoo! ♪
♪ We gotta bring
Both sides together ♪
♪ Like champagne and leather ♪
♪ Like birds of a feather
We'll fly ♪
♪ Like rain on a sunny day ♪
♪ Like a million dollars
That you're givin' away ♪
♪ Like a stray dog On
the freeway We'll fly ♪
♪ 'Cause we're all
Like a team ♪
♪ Livin' inside a dream ♪
♪ You and me doin' our thing ♪
♪ And we'll fly ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Unbelievable, super cool
Outrageous and amazing ♪
♪ Phenomenal, fantastic
So incredible ♪
♪ Woo-hoo! ♪
♪ Unbelievable, super cool
Outrageous and amazing ♪
♪ Phenomenal, fantastic
So incredible ♪
♪ Woo-hoo! ♪
♪ And we're back ♪
♪ And still loving
The credits ♪
♪ Can't wait to see the one
About the person who edits ♪
♪ And even better than that
Is who edits the credits ♪
♪ I bet I'll never forget it 'Cause
once I read it, then I read it ♪
♪ I go to the theater
About 90 minutes late ♪
♪ Skip the whole dang movie
'Cause the credits are great ♪
♪ Now, if you're Gonna be
featured On a movie song ♪
♪ The credits is the part
That you wanna be on! ♪
[man 1] Yeah,
I like to watch the credits.
♪ Super cool ♪
♪ I can't believe
They got Chris Cunnington ♪
♪ To be
the stereoscopic supervisor ♪
♪ Timothy Smith
Is my favorite producer ♪
[man 2] I just came to see This
movie For the associate producing.
[woman] Yes!
Super cool!
♪ Unbelievable, super cool
Outrageous and amazing ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ Phenomenal, fantastic
So incredible ♪
♪ Woo-hoo! ♪
♪ Oh, snap
It's time for the actors ♪
♪ The ones who elicit
All the joy and the laughter ♪
♪ In the voiceover studio,
slaving away ♪
♪ They had to work Almost
four whole hours A day ♪
♪ It's a nightmare ♪
♪ There's so much strain
On the brain ♪
♪ And their only compensation
Is the money and fame ♪
♪ Without the human element
It's just zeroes and ones ♪
♪ That's why When we pay 'em
the money We pay 'em tons ♪
♪ And we're still
In the song ♪
♪ How long are these credits?
'Cause they seem long ♪
♪ Which is great ♪
♪ 'Cause we
La-la-la-la-love 'em ♪
♪ I wanna wrap my arms around
And ha-ha-ha-ha-hug 'em ♪
♪ If they were a person
I would marry the credits ♪
♪ And on our honeymoon We
would play tennis In Venice ♪
♪ I'll grow old
With the credits ♪
♪ And share a code
To our debits ♪
♪ And then
Move outside of Paris ♪
♪ And raise a farm
Full of ferrets ♪
♪ Unbelievable, super cool
Outrageous and amazing ♪
♪ Super cool! ♪
♪ Phenomenal, fantastic
So incredible ♪
♪ Woo-hoo! ♪
♪ Unbelievable, super cool
Outrageous and amazing ♪
♪ Super cool! ♪
♪ Phenomenal, fantastic
So incredible ♪
♪ Woo-hoo! ♪
♪ Everything is super cool
right now ♪
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ Everything is awesome here
right now ♪
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ Everything is super cool Right now
Hey, hey, everything ♪
♪ Everything is awesome
here Right now Hey, hey ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ Everything is super
cool Right now Hey, hey ♪
♪ Everything is awesome here
Right now ♪
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ Everything is super cool
Right now ♪
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ Everything is awesome
here Right now Hey, hey ♪
♪ This song's gonna
Get stuck inside your ♪
♪ This song's gonna get stuck
Inside your head ♪
♪ This song's gonna
Get stuck inside your ♪
♪ This song's gonna get stuck
Inside your head ♪
♪ It's so catchy, catchy ♪
♪ It's such a catchy song ♪
♪ It'll make you happy,
happy ♪
♪ Don't try to fight it,
sing along ♪
♪ This song's gonna
Get stuck inside your ♪
Get stuck inside you ♪
♪ This song's gonna
♪ Run, but you can't hide,
I'll find you Sun so bright ♪
♪ My bling bling blind you ♪
♪ Sing this song
I must remind your ♪
♪ Everybody real loud,
Scream and then shout ♪
♪ Everybody in the house Got
it comin' From they mouth ♪
♪ Wait a minute
Let me get 'em ♪
♪ Can't help the rhythm
Stuck in your system ♪
♪ I'm goin' to the top
Everybody goin' to the top ♪
♪ Everybody head gon' rock
Everybody say, "Don't stop" ♪
♪ Everybody say, "Don't stop"
Ooh ♪
♪ This song's gonna
Get stuck inside your ♪
Get stuck inside your head ♪
♪ This song's gonna
Get stuck inside your ♪
Get stuck inside your head ♪
♪ It's so catchy, catchy ♪
♪ It's such a catchy song ♪
♪ It'll make you happy,
happy ♪
♪ Don't try to fight it,
sing along ♪
♪ This song's gonna
Get stuck inside your ♪
Get stuck inside your head ♪
♪ There is nothin'
That you can do ♪
That you can say ♪
♪ This song is stuck
On replay ♪
♪ You gotta sing it
Every single day ♪
♪ From the mornin'
And through the night ♪
♪ I got 'em movin'
From left to right ♪
♪ And if you wonder
Who's to blame ♪
♪ Yeah, it's me
Stuck in they brain ♪
♪ Like a permanent stain
And it won't change ♪
♪ Even if you go insane ♪
♪ This song
Is now in your brain ♪
♪ And in your brain
It will remain ♪
♪ This song is now stuck
Inside your ♪
Inside your head ♪
♪ This song is now stuck
Inside your ♪
Inside your head ♪
♪ 'Cause it's so catchy,
catchy ♪
♪ It's such a catchy song ♪
♪ It'll make you happy,
happy ♪
♪ Don't try to fight it,
sing along ♪
♪ This song's gonna
Get stuck inside your ♪
Get stuck inside your head ♪
♪ This song's gonna
Get stuck inside your ♪
Get stuck inside your head ♪
♪ Come together now ♪
♪ I'm cookie and you're cream,
sugar gasoline ♪
♪ You're the kick,
I'm the snare Let's go make a beat ♪
♪ You build, I knock it down
You're a verb, I'm a noun ♪
♪ You swerve, I lean
We walk down the same street ♪
♪ I'm gas, you're the brake
Here and wide awake ♪
♪ Together we can drive All
night With the windows down ♪
♪ You're AC, I'm the heat
Scraped knees, concrete ♪
♪ You make me better
So let's come together now ♪
♪ Come together now ♪
♪ Square to a hexagon
More sides, less wrong ♪
♪ Pepsi, Coke
Then you mix a little ice ♪
♪ Street signs in camouflage
All day "blah blah blah" ♪
♪ Got no time to waste
Paid the asking price ♪
♪ I paint inside the lines
Takes me too much time ♪
♪ You're a mess
And that's all I want to be ♪
♪ Loosen up a bit
Flex and take the hit ♪
♪ If I make you better
Then let's come together now ♪
♪ Come together now ♪
[scatting]
♪ Can we get together today? ♪
♪ Or are we more different
Than not? ♪
♪ I'm cold and you're hot ♪
♪ Are we just stuck
In our ways? ♪
♪ Call my friend up ♪
♪ Yeah, tell me what you got ♪
♪ Oh, we're opposite stuff ♪
♪ We're sandals and socks ♪
♪ We're nerds
And we're jocks ♪
♪ And we're
Better off together ♪
♪ We got to hang out ♪
♪ 'Cause we're better off to ♪
♪ We can work together
For sure ♪
♪ Na na ♪
♪ Even though you fly
First class ♪
♪ And I'm at the back ♪
♪ You're hilarious
I'm a bore ♪
♪ Na na ♪
♪ And the choir starts up ♪
♪ Yeah, show me what you got ♪
♪ Oh, we're different things ♪
♪ We're MJ and Prince ♪
♪ We're concrete and bling ♪
♪ But we're
Better off together ♪
♪ We got to hang out ♪
♪ 'Cause we're better ♪
♪ Hello, me and you ♪
♪ Na na na na ♪
♪ We're better as a two ♪
♪ Even though we're different
We're the same ♪
♪ We've got to work it out ♪
♪ Before it drives us insane ♪
♪ Hello, me and you ♪
♪ Na na na na ♪
♪ We've got to start
Playing in time ♪
♪ Can there be
A marriage of minds? ♪
♪ Can we be alike? ♪
♪ Can we turn water to wine? ♪
♪ Or is too much fuss? ♪
♪ Are you all that I'm not? ♪
♪ Oh, we're far apart ♪
♪ We're casual and smart ♪
♪ We're logic and art ♪
♪ And we're
Better off together ♪
♪ We got to hang out ♪
♪ 'Cause we're better ♪
♪ Hello, me and you ♪
♪ Na na na na ♪
♪ We're better as a two ♪
♪ Even though we're different
We're the same ♪
♪ So get into the rocket ♪
♪ 'Cause we're going
To space ♪
♪ Hello, me and you ♪
♪ Na na na na ♪
Subtitles by explosiveskull